oh dear
it's come to this the finale of season
six and my goodness are we going out in
style it's been a fantastic season my
first season it doesn't even really feel
like it doesn't really feel like it does
it because we've accomplished so much
but i definitely want to make sure we go
out in style so i've compiled a little
list of the things that i'd like to do
this episode
before
i leave season six now remember i'm not
leaving hermitcraft don't be silly don't
be silly however i will be ending season
six and i will be back when season seven
starts which will actually be
sooner than you think
maybe even in a week
yep hermitcraft season seven will be
starting very very shortly i don't know
the exact date but
i'm excited it's going to be a few days
at least but my goodness so let's start
with what we want to do prepare to kill
iskall kill iskaw final sahara meeting
admit my biggest secret play some
minigames show my best bits and launch
and leave okay well
let's start with number one then
the best one prepare to kill iskall now
i need to meet up very shortly with
impulse because i have prepared this
very odd and strange contraption here
that's meant to give some sort of
indication of our plan so let's meet up
with impulse and go over how we're going
to deliver
this demise for iskall
hello impulse
hello again are you ready for this
i am i am super excited i i can't i
can't stop smiling because i'm so
excited for what we're putting together
this episode so we've already sort of
planned everything out but this is like
a physical representation of what we're
going to be putting together so just so
the audience understands our plan we're
already like a few days into our one
week time so we've actually got to crack
on and get this done
so
it's split into two halves my half and
then impulse is half that way we can we
can work on it without crazy time zone
issues so
let's go over what i'm going to do now
mine is gonna be somewhat of like a
actiony
uh like play type thing where i'm gonna
have a custom jukebox it's gonna do some
weird and wacky things iskall is gonna
go in the minecart and he's gonna be
pushed around my play is going to tell a
weird and wonderful story and then boom
we hit impulses section which is going
to be
redstone of course
this is my representation of
this is in my mind this is what you're
doing this is exactly what i had planned
actually
oh it's gonna be good i'm gonna build up
a bit of a rube goldberg type machine to
send him through and he won't know
when he's gonna actually die i think
there's gonna be a lot of little jump
scares for him and uh yeah in the end of
course he's gonna get his but i think
we're gonna save
that for you know later it's gonna be a
secret the actual way that iskall's
going to be demised it'll be the end of
all this so don't you panic and uh it
will be a nice secret and a surprise
because i don't want anyone spoiling it
right
oh man this is gonna be fun but we got
lots of work to do this is gonna be
amazing okay let's let's get cracking so
let's get started on the demise iskall
train
this is going to be absolutely
incredible so the first thing that we've
got to do is fill this out so this is a
slightly enlarged version of what we're
doing impulse has already done some
redstone stuff to make him go at the
right pace
but now it's my turn to actually get
this going so if you didn't understand
this guy's going to go along this track
he's going to stop he's going to watch
the scene that happens here and it's
going to be all resource pack driven
there's going to be a music it's it's
honestly this should be really funny
it's going to take a lot of work to get
this right
but i've got my black concrete powder so
let's get started on this time lapse so
this time lapse is going to be just
quick i mean to be honest with you i'm
basically just making big boxes and each
one is going to be a stage the stage is
going to be exactly the same throughout
and i'm hoping to tell a story the main
thing that i wanted to say is that we
have created a custom resource pack so i
did a little bit of voice acting now
i've never done this before so i don't
know if it's absolutely awful or not but
i kind of like dave made a silly voice
anyway you're gonna see i've built this
thing it took absolutely ages let's go
several hours later and we have
completed it so what i've made is a
little kitchen because
this is going to tell a story iskall's
going to go in a minecart right here
it's going to go round timed perfectly
with a custom music disc right here um
because obviously there's nothing here
at the moment so there's going to be a
couple of actors on the stage and
there's something to do with diorite as
i said i did a little voice over i don't
know how good it sounds but listen
welcome to the ride of your life for
your safety please keep your hands and
feet inside the vehicle at all times
we wouldn't want you to get hurt see
here we witness the purge okay i don't
want to spoil too much i don't spoil too
much so we've got a custom music disc
we're going to send iskall round for the
story and then it drops the bass drops
the beat into impulse's half but i've
actually
there's there's so much going on for
this finale everyone's trying to wrap up
i think so i actually need to go over to
sahara where there is a meeting going on
the final sahara meeting
and look what is that what an oh who's
put an ugly addition into this
we're
win
winner
mumbo really
really okay right i'm gonna message iska
mumbo and we're gonna get this final
sahara meeting underway
gentlemen
it's come to this the end of the season
the final meeting of sahara
woo
that's not that's not really a woo
moment mumbai
sorry ah
i spoke with ren the other day on the
customers our hotline
and i realized throughout this entire
season
yeah we've only had one
failure with zara
pretty
yeah and that was when green put up a
there hasn't been a single customer
complaint
everything's been working
except for when green potato yeah see
well that's a straight apply because
we've had so many custom customer
complaints all the orders came in super
late some of them were seriously wrong
but somehow we've made some diamonds
really have we actually i mean well we
made diamonds i don't actually know if
we
you know i was going to say made
we've made diamonds have we
made have we broken even is that a big
question we've got diamonds but whether
we've actually made a profit i i have no
idea
we've had we've had a lot of costs
building this thing
yes yeah
i mean i mean iskall we've spent
how much on red stuff we've spent a lot
on redstone
a lot honestly i actually
don't really know but i think i've
probably i've probably spent 800
diamonds 500 diamonds 600 good six okay
had it on the paper six okay
pieces of diamonds on cherry computers
sahara is basically just given why
didn't you know this is this is scar
shop really
we've just given him all of our diamonds
i i've definitely i
i'm with this guy i don't i don't really
know we really should have kept better
accounts yeah definitely i mean we
probably it's fair to say that we've
spent a thousand diamonds all together
on all the redstone components and that
sort of stuff in the warehouse and
yeah and hiring hiring ariana griande
wasn't cheap like she charges a lot for
her appearances
we spent a lot on the uh the grand
opening that wasn't cheap um getting
touched
news all that stuff
dude
when we were doing those things you
never mentioned that there was any
really any much of a cost involved you
just said
to ariana griande of course or maybe her
agent i don't know
the point is they're gone so
it's cost
gone right but i don't remember wearing
diamonds it was it was quite a few
did you spend any diamonds on anything
material oh no i got the concrete myself
it was mainly mainly ariana grande the
hermit news the grand opening all the
fireworks all that kind of you know
the marketing marketing budget
did you buy the fireworks as well you
you bought the fireworks i get through a
lot of fireworks boys i've got gun
powder farm i have paper farm i used it
all
and that's true
okay he did yeah
um would that right i mean this chair
you you got this yourself oh yeah no no
no i paid for this jelly and this this
was an expense
what else what the trousers you wearing
the shoes what they did that haircut is
that an expensive girl what have you
been spending the day
possibly look at that look at it
i mean if you look at the back of my
head it looks like a waffle
that's true
waffle expenses through you're blasting
me you guys don't expect waffles oh my
goodness that's the
[Music]
yes i'm actually surprised how long it
took you guys i noticed it i didn't even
see that it says winner
i genuinely thought i genuinely thought
they had made a princess chair and i was
like that's fitting
nope
i am the winner so i've won the cheap
state yeah
is not the most annoying chair that's
ever existed
yeah and you have expensive chairs
sahara sahara diamonds cost
costing chair fantastic okay so how look
okay
we've spent a lot of diamonds clearly
things that costs have gone a little bit
at hand nobody really saw that coming um
me and iskall thought we were on top of
the costs and things we hadn't realized
that we were chucking diamonds left
right and center to all sorts of
different
different ventures um so
how many diamonds have we made i don't
know but we've definitely spent
170 170 blocks
just leads to you know yeah so you know
you spent you spent money on redstone i
spent money on ariana grande so let's
just leave it at that
let's get down to brass tacks let's go
and check how many diamonds we've
actually got in the pile here's the pile
of diamonds
so here's our pot oh man i don't i can't
be bothered to count them all right
let's let's start smashing these down
it's solid yeah oh mate maybe it's a
little bit hollow oh yeah
yeah it's solid
oh yeah hi guys yeah maybe okay so maybe
i made it look like we have more
diamonds than we do
i was gonna say
it's all peruse
i built this and i fooled myself into
thinking we had more diamonds than we
really do right let's um let's pop these
into a sugar box
plus
64.
uh is that all of them is that one of
them
made a
loss well better luck
give me a second guys give me a second i
i i have some diamond blocks
give me give me give me a second i spent
all my diamond blocks
sorry i'm coming back guys oh look at
that oh look at that we made a profit
yeah we made a profit
we broke even with mother break even we
made a problem five blocks and five
diamonds
uh i say mumbo you take two i take two
angry and you take one and some carrots
i mean oh my carrots
that's what i'm saying
what is the return on investment in
terms of pretend percentage-wise of the
amount of diamond blocks
compared to the return i would say
listen
this was a great project but overall it
was a financial disaster
you know next season
maybe with a little bit of a head start
we can we can do something bigger
and better than this
yeah yes so
sahara
i'm getting instead instead of instead
of just splitting those five diamond
blocks why don't we send those to season
seven with us as our initial investment
into whatever we do next season five
diamond blocks
i mean how how do we send them i mean
surely sending them is gonna cost about
well uh yeah maybe we'll use the the 60
the two nearly three stacks of diamonds
um to pay for the rocket that sends uh
the five diamond blocks right
oh yeah investing this entire window all
right i'll get my redstone gear oh is he
gonna are you gonna make
oh is this mumbo jumbo rocket time i
mean it doesn't does it need to look
like a rocket just got to send it off
into the sphere this is the most high
pressured redstone build i've ever done
in my entire life there's a lot of fresh
feel like the whole world
is watching me right green if you do the
honors and just and stack the uh the old
diamond blocks on top of that piston
there let's see if you can follow this
instruction
we lost one oh gosh
without
here we go as we do it we have to shout
we broke even wait wait wait wait wait
the three i feel three is bad can we
start with
twenty no no no no no no
two okay five one
[Laughter]
look all right okay and we're away
oh my goodness me
what's happening to it
oh oh i i i i've realized what i've done
wrong
[Music]
why are we celebrating diamonds
disappearing
oh yeah
bye diamond i needed to get green a new
hair profit now that the diamonds have
taken off it's time to set up iscao's
demise impulse and i are completely
finished
and it's time to do a little bit of
testing and then get iskall over here to
actually
do his demise i mean we paid good
diamonds for this so my goodness this
better be good
impulse is your half completely finished
my half is completely finished man i'm
super excited about it okay mine is also
finished so i need to show you exactly
what's going on because i really need
your help we're going to have to do a
little bit of rehearsals for this you
kind of know what's going on but i
haven't actually given you firm
instructions so okay i'm i'm sending
iskall through like a documentary style
thing from the 50s and we're gonna be
the actors for this now i'm gonna what
i'm gonna do is i'm gonna put you in the
minecart and i will sort of uh i'll do
half of the acting and then you can kind
of get an idea for it
okay
we've set up this custom music disc as
you know um so get in the minecart and
i'll uh i'll i'll do the thing you ready
okay
here we go to the ride of your life your
safety please keep your hands and feet
inside the vehicle at all times we
wouldn't want you to get hurt oh there
you are
here we witness the perfect hermit
crosshall
messier stays at home while the
redstoner goes out during the day's work
oh look here he is now so is going to
enter in or you playing the builder
prepared
it's none other than his favorite meal
swedish meatballs
it really is the perfect hermit
household
oh my goodness where am i going now
so you got a pretty good idea of what my
half is gonna look like right roughly
speaking we've now tweaked the time so
it works even better now i'm i'm
desperate to see what you've done can i
um we're gonna sit through it again and
then yep uh i'll meet you at the end
okay
sounds good all right welcome to the
rock
goodbye enjoy the ride korean
what
good night
oh my
impulse
[Laughter]
wait for it you love this next part
oh my goodness
what's gonna happen oh
come on be careful
oh
okay that was phenomenal
that this is gonna be the best thing
ever okay let's get this scale in here
right now we need to do this before
anything breaks okay
right now okay i blacked out the the
last few seconds because the actual
method of his destruction would want to
keep secret as much as possible okay
great are we ready i think we're ready i
am ready yes i got to refill that
diorite that filled your pockets but yes
other than that i'm ready all right
let's go let's go prepare and get iskall
in here asap
sounds good welcome misskow
uh you're probably surprised to see me
here
for a little bit yep
so what's happened here is uh i went
half z with it with impulse on this so
that i could be super involved and we've
kind of gone literally halves so i've
done half of your device and impulse has
done half of your demise and i think
you'll be able to tell who did which bit
but you know we'll leave that as a
surprise
it's gonna be good i can't believe you
guys did this so basically
impulse you won the auction and then
did you how did how did green get he
gave me some diamonds to be part of it i
was like yeah let's do it man let's team
up paid for this i paid for this
experience
so this is the ride of your life dude
are you
you ready
i guess yeah you're gonna have to pull
your items in that chest because you are
going to die
i am going to die that that sounds that
just sounds so scary dude
it's been so long we didn't test this
with a dragon head on i hope that
i shouldn't have kept anything i can't
take that off but hold on just one last
time i want to see since last death 7.38
days
wow no afk time congrats man that is
impressive
okay so um this is kind of a solo
experience for you so
we're actually gonna leave you to it and
um i think we'll have to say enjoy the
ride right impulse exactly man enjoy the
ride of your life all right so i am i'm
just terribly scared
yeah you should be
you really should be you really should
be okay right let's we're gonna go
backstage um good luck iskal we'll uh
we'll see you at the other end
bye
ready uh
yep
three
oh i'm so scared i'm shaking
what's gonna happen i'm all alone
welcome to the ride of your life for
your safety please keep your hands and
feet inside the vehicle at all times we
wouldn't want you to get hurt
here we witness the perfect hermit
household the builder stays at home
while the redstoner goes out during the
day to work
oh look here he is now
what has the builder prepared for dinner
tonight
it's none other than his favorite meal
swedish meatballs this really is the
perfect hermit household
this is like not as simple as they first
appear
what
the builder has bought a gift for the
household a lovely direct statue surely
this will go down a treat let's see what
the hard-working redstoner has to say
burn it yes
good he seems to hate it yes good beat
him beat him up
and then i'm going again perhaps not all
is dandy in this hermitcraft household
after all let's see what happens next oh
no
korean
oh no
it seems the builder has acquired a
taste for diorite and has decorated the
entire house with it
surely our hard-working redstoner will
help the builder through this troubling
obsession no
no no
oh dear yes it seems that he would
rather see the house blown to
smithereens
will this discourse be solved with a
candid conversation
let's find out
[Laughter]
shock the redstoner has left the builder
alone with the diorite
it seems the builder is plotting some
kind of revenge
how will this thrilling tale end for our
hard-working redstone hermit there's
only one way to find out
enjoy the ride iskall85
to your demise
oh
my
okay
okay yes no
is this it
is this it oh that's good okay scallion
we're safe oh i'm on half hard i'm half
heart apart
oh my goodness
i don't know the run game the run game
is here
that's looking awesome but that that
looks scary
no no no no no
no
what
what just happened i was alive i'm
invincible i'm invincible
i'm still alive
[Laughter]
[Music]
he just punched me to death
after all of this
i die
from getting punched
and i'm pretty sure
i'm pretty sure that was at the
uh at my headband shop
impulse i think we should take a bow for
our little acting skills there
thank you thank you
well
done that's well done but can i just ask
what in the world korean well um
could you tell who did what what side of
the uh which side of the demise can you
tell who did what half yeah
yeah i think i i think i got it the the
redstoner and the builder i see how it
is
i gotta say i must i must get a copy of
that suit okay uh i will loan it to you
for sure that is a very fancy suit i do
approve of it
now this was this was incredible
i mean i'm kind of happy i'm i know i
just died
but i'm cut wait a minute by the way
you punched me grian
you can keep it
here's another one of you what
that that that escalator you went up
it's actually the escalator it's the
diorite escalator
yes the ascalium bouncy room right you
that was so scary i had half a heart
through that room
for sure i'm gonna die in one of these
bombs could have been anything that was
the idea
and then i drove up towards a dispenser
thinking okay well here comes the arrow
and then i drove up i drove through a
lava room did you guys know that and the
arrows didn't hit me they just went
right in front of my face every single
time no it's almost it's almost like we
planned this impulse exactly right
but i can't believe it actually went to
big big brain big brain redstone there
well done took us a week but we did it
did i get killed in my own hit hit bam
room
you did
he did yep
yeah
for sure oh yeah
it was worth it thank you it was totally
worth a week's worth of work and a lot
of diamonds and now i'm going to leave
the building
see you builder
that went
better than i could have possibly ever
expected and i'll tell you what i'm
gonna i'm gonna leave this this dragon
head uh for you guys in the world
download so i'm gonna i'm gonna keep
hold of that um but i've actually had a
couple of messages from bdubs and doc
who are both interested in buying my
mansion in the mini game district so
let's head on over there and see what we
can do
gentlemen
welcome to
this little meeting here so i noticed
that you bdubs and doc have both
messaged me that you're interested in
the house and you've both laid claim to
it with a with a a sign but i'll tell
you what no no
diamonds have not exchanged hands i know
i was selling it for minus 10 diamonds
but i haven't given you anything so it's
currently technically unsold
so finders keepers though you know
finders keepers you know no no no wait
wait
i spoke with him like a year ago about
this
mm-hmm
a year ago but you didn't put the sign
see i put the sign here this birch sign
the sign that was here mine
yeah
that's mine now yeah the year ago might
be a lie but i really want it it's such
a beautiful house
look it's right there the ufo is over
there prime real estate it's been for
sale for a long time and no one's shown
any interest and then all of a sudden
both of you guys turn up so you know
what we're gonna do we're gonna we're
gonna have an auction and you guys can
can battle it out okay
oh i'm ready good look at that
good
all right so i'm rich i'm rich i can do
this okay all right we'll start the
bidding then at the current price of
minus 10 diamonds that means i'll pay
okay b dubs you're a minus 10. do i have
any more minus five minus five dollars
minus five the dog i will give you five
diamonds do we have zero free absolutely
free
minus one diamond
diamond for it minus one diamond a b
double o
zero zero here zero zero diamonds have
we got any other bidders we're gonna go
up we're gonna go to ten diamonds we're
going to go as high as 10. now we're now
we're actually paying now we're paying
for that we were going to get down i
hope you're happy this is good great job
and now we're paying for it it's a giant
house
okay i'll pay i'll pay ten diamonds ten
dollars
do i see 20
yes i'll do 20. 20 or b double o
going once
okay 40 40 40 40 diamonds
40 diamonds doc m77 do i see a raise on
that
forty five
this is this natural spruce wood you
made this out
wait do you even have that can you back
it up i have that i have more and i'm
not going to tell you how much okay okay
do i hear do i hear any more than 45 if
not i will 50 50 diamonds
50 diamonds 50
50 is all i got i guess i only have 50.
50. i'll do 50 as well sold for 50
diamonds each you can both have half the
house for 50 diamonds
sold you both you both put in 50 and i i
have the hammer kablooey sold
i'll take that
uh you can have the right hand side b
dubs and doc you can have the left side
that's the hundred diamonds that i
wanted i'm out good luck enjoy your
house uh have fun and good day i wanted
the right side that worked out perfect
um
okay then
wonderful
so there's just a couple more things
left to do on my checklist and then
this season will come to
an end a proper end
let's take a quick look here
prepare to kill iscow kill this gal
final sahara meeting i didn't get to
play any mini games
um so there's only a couple things left
so i've got to admit
my biggest secret
all right let's let's get that out the
way
now i know it may come as a shock to
many of you here
but here look at this
you see this
it was me
the whole time
i
was poultry man
i don't
believe it
i know i've had to come clean
because
i'm going to leave
the mask behind
for the next person
that comes to season 6 world download
map maybe you will be able to don the
mask so good luck and i will finally
admit
it
was i
green
that
was
poultry man
dun dun dun
plot twist
big plot twist
there's also something else i i need to
admit as well um but it's a little bit
strange okay so many people remember in
um a very specific ghost that appeared
in people's episodes randomly and then
vanished um
yeah i didn't really do anything with it
i was just kind of freaking people out
yeah that was me as well look at this i
i've got a shulker box around the corner
here
it's my salmon kit i've got invisibility
potions and milk and pickles so what i
would do is i'd find someone recording
i'd uh i'd i'd go invisible
but i'd pop the head on
i'd uh i'd go invisible
i'd wait until i was sure that they were
recording and i would run i'd do
something like this i'd go and i'd run
and then i'd drop the pickle i'd
literally just chop the pickle
job done
um but since it's the end of the season
i'm going to admit
it was me
it was all me
yeah so big reveal over salmon ghost was
nothing more than a little prank
and uh
yeah i wish i did something more with
that but i didn't i didn't i just i i
don't know what it was i i it was fun
though so i think
that's actually pretty much
everything
um
yeah now it's time to
launch and leave
so
yeah i think that's
that's what we're gonna do
we're gonna say goodbye
so right i'm gonna leave
iskall's demise head
my gear
for anyone to enjoy
it's the g hat and the g boots and the
elytra all of my tools and gears
for you guys to use
it's all set up i don't know if this is
actually going to work but we're about
to find out
goodbye season six hello season seven
where on earth did that arrow go
that was
so far off
okay maybe we're gonna have to do it
this way
all right
goodbye season six hello season seven
you know i'm not entirely surprised that
the rocket didn't work
not entirely surprised at all
i'ma simplify this right down
to its bare components
this doesn't work i give up oh it's
going it's going it's going quick get in
get in get in it's leaving without me
i'm taking damage
that's cool you know that's cool i don't
want to i don't want to take damage i'll
just i'll just stand on it shall i let's
get rid of all this stuff
bye everyone bye season six
bye let's get rid of that can't take
anything with me
all right
here we go
take it away now while we're heading out
like like i'm i i'm a head out um so
i've prepared
my favorite moment from every single
episode on hermitcraft one from each and
just as we're about to leave
i think i'm going to play it for you
so
i think all there is left to say
is
thank you
so much for this season it's been
absolutely incredible
i've learned so much but there's still
a lot for me to learn
and in season seven we're definitely
gonna do that so please enjoy
the best bits from every episode
on hermitcraft thank you very much for
watching
i'll see you
only next week
for season seven
enjoy
and
for the final time but not really the
final time i'm not quitting hermitcraft
season seven we'll be starting next week
good bye
there's probably one thing that you
should know about me is that i'm not
like the other hermits you see i'm a
little bit different i don't do things
perhaps the most efficiently or the best
way
my goal here is to have as much fun as
possible
okay i i do build a lot that's true
but i mainly want to have the best time
that i possibly can on this server this
is probably my favorite thing about this
cow farm is that they're all in there
you flip this and the hill bounce up and
down boing boing boing boing boing boing
boing boing boing boing boing no
no no no no no no no
[Music]
so i went to his base
i spawned a lot of chickens all over the
island he still didn't notice so i put
the chickens down in his bunker and then
he finally came up i milked his cows and
i scarfed it was brilliant and why are
they all just chilling out there oh no
they've decided to move now
i feel like there's got to be someone
responsible for this
there he is he's afk as usual ow
i don't think i was supposed to be in
here maybe that was anti-green
technology going on and
apparent
what
hey mamba let's go and say hello shall
we
oh
i forgot about fall damage again who is
that
don't pull the lever that's what you
said right
that is what it said so i went maybe the
lever is on and i just have to turn it
off so i went like this and then this
happened
okay so you arrive it says hey guys i
turned myself into a pickle jump on in
okay so this is what i've got don't
touch they are picklish this water can
be a little cumbersome get it cucumber
i've had a few messages from some of the
other hermits telling me that they're
not too happy with the design of my shop
and then i heard yep there it is iskall
has put something on the top now i
haven't actually seen this until now
it's a massive pickle coming out the top
of my pickle jar what does this say
you're a pickle harry does anybody need
testing
we'll we'll test anything for six
diamonds hello
someone's gonna hire me eventually right
let's go up and have a look at this
mumbo shop this is going to be
interesting there doesn't seem to be
anything here
please read
congratulations you just bought a
spoiler three diamonds must be deposited
in the chest immediately come back soon
ah
do we both go through
no no no no no
no no no free and free
no
enough enough enough enough
oh away he goes
bye gevin
from him
what no jevin
how did jevin fell off
uh oh mumbo jumbo you are afk
i'm gonna take that mustache away
[Music]
he went
[Laughter]
i found him i found him let's see him
panic he's panicking he's panicking
he's punching me
[Laughter]
but this meant
all of these
inexplicable mistakes
cost me 13 hours of time and that is no
exaggeration 13 hours to make this one
map oh my goodness this is so bizarre
oops
you might actually find that by accident
if you're just like looking around
so this is really strange so this is the
meeting room see i know there's a wall
there i think it's just my mind playing
tricks on me but i know there's a wall
directly here you can't tell at all is
this something that you want me to crack
on i'll be open i'll be i'll be honest
with you i didn't expect you to fall for
it
wait yeah well i expected it to explode
no you have to take out the bottom block
or you have to shoot them do you want to
do it at the same time
[Laughter]
do you think he knows we're here
no go on press it again see if something
happens
what's he doing
[Laughter]
no no no no no no no no no no no no i
didn't mean it i didn't mean it
and everything is repaired and we have a
bunch of levels as well
i'd say all in all that was pretty
successful little grind that we'd
how
i wasn't even going that you are kidding
me
poultry man is back
look at his little face
look at his face
he's he's gonna come back and he's gonna
be he's gonna know exactly what's
happened here one
[Applause]
yes
[Laughter]
what
ah he's escaping
no no no no no need to let him he's in
he's in he's in he's
quickly quickly run where are you
go go go go go go go go go go go
[Music]
did he get him
no
[Laughter]
here we see the sweden shorts making his
fifth attempt
it's a good shot
it's a good drive
oh that was a cracking shot you got so
lucky
and he's made it across the waterway
with clear view to the end
this is the kind of shot we've come to
expect from the sweden shorts
[Laughter]
i look so weird without a fringe i
should always have my hair on i'm a bit
like mumbo as soon as i take off my hair
i look really strange
look so this is my fringe it's kind of
like my whole thing it's my identity but
if i take it off
i look just as strange as mumbo
i died in your pickle dude
this is an awkward moment
i didn't even die from dying
i just fell to my death i've trapped
myself in here with you and i'm gonna
leave the fork of friendship right there
but i kind of want to leave a sign for
you no wait i don't even need to leave a
sign i'll just leave a green head there
he's gonna know maybe
maybe maybe i should make it very clear
who left this this cursor binding head
go on him
i want i do i do what is wrong with this
hold on all right you ready so it's
together forever in there
ready
got him
[Music]
why is messing with mumbo so much fun
with obsidian here it says
if you use a pickaxe on these i will no
hmm
give it a go with the old silk machine
oh
oh my goodness
oh no
oh what a tragedy
we're off
oh dear here we go
oh no
now the lag lag
it's hurting it it lagged me into the
floor whoa
well what did we get from that hey
there's some emeralds
two stacks of tnt was totally worth it
ren
you've just been poultry manned oh no
i'm almost i'm almost out of eggs what
kind of poultry man runs out of eggs
large
where's he gone
[Music]
and
there we go
that's like the best door in the world
that's amazing i am impressed with that
they're going to come for a jacuzzi with
their latest client they're going to
right click this and this is what
they're going to see
[Laughter]
the client may change their mind i'll
just say that
[Laughter]
this is gonna be good though this is
gonna be good oh
bruh
[Applause]
let me show you
come over here
how did you do that how did you do that
the g team okay now hear me out you're
all thinking oh
what's that all about well everyone here
has a g in their name green
tango
see it all works right
zombie glio
grass monster
go hills hi gavin it works so well now
can i sleep before that creeper sees me
and blows me up
yes
[Laughter]
if you can't beat them join them i'll be
here when you get back mumbo
i'll be here
ah
ah he's back
hello
hello yes you have a problem and it's
not me we need to get out of here
i'm trying to punch oh
sorry mama
i'm gonna go i'm gonna head off and do
some mold duties then i'll get right to
it you know i'm a hard working guy you
gotta wait until they ask you to join
the team you can't just walk into their
base and be like hey guys i'm a mole you
gotta wait you gotta wait for them to
ask you to be on the team yeah right
yeah yeah oh maybe this is a bad idea
it's gal this is a bad idea immediately
he's just gonna walk in and tell him
already i'm just panicking inside to be
honest okay
i've got this i i'm look at my mustache
you can't trick me although i am
actually going to
mine this because i want to know how
this blows up
oh
where are you
hello did i just imagine you talking
what is going on i'm here i'm in the
room can you see me
yes
dude what is going on
what is going on i think maybe my client
oh dude
wow what
oh bro that's genius quick quick there's
no stress i cannot stress enough that
there's no time where what are you doing
stress
we need horses
look
okay right come chill
chill stress
right here come on
they said press the button twice that's
all you had to do press the button twice
now watch watch this
oh
hit
button behind castle
number two
my instructions are imprinted on the
fish
so where's the castle number two all
right it could be one of these
no
oh there it is
that's so cool that is so so cool anyway
all right orders create a weapon for
team star but rig it to blow up when one
of them uses it and blame someone on the
g team if they ask
right puff of fish here i come
and yep okay
there's really there there's really not
there's not a lot you can do
yeah there's really not a lot you can oh
i'm back in my base oh my god
i found something i found something okay
so i can see one of their flags no way
that was dude
genius um they're still am i allowed to
go through here i mean yeah yeah yeah
there's still phantoms here i've i've
got
did we just go in
oh oh no oh that made me jump oh that
made me jump so much dude quickly
run to the base
false was slain by iscow
excuse me oh there's no enough time i've
got the banner i got the banner i'm
going in i'm going again does this mean
we win i better get it okay let's play
it fair let's get it to all the other
ones we're almost there
flag captured flag captured
captured
did we run out of lives
we might have just lost the last life
as the flag has been captured
it's wait that's it we we win
unbelievable can't wait
i said i said don't don't worry i'll get
back to my stuff now
yeah i'll i'll get back to my stuff now
i'll be off
when is he gonna realize
look it's been nice seeing you mate i'll
i'll see you soon
it's been really what is
[Laughter]
as i was saying it's been nice to see
you oh it's no better it's not better
you know what just see you bye
he's
i think he's no he's not afk
he hasn't seen
oh my goodness
hold on i've got i've got a prank
since wally doesn't know
since he hasn't got a clue
quickly
sub to green
i'm gonna give him a taste of his own
medicine
[Laughter]
on your right you'll see stress
monster's castle
founded at the beginning of the season
and is continually being worked on to
this day
and if you look to the left you will see
some polar bears in their natural
habitat it's floating
and on your left you will see the random
crafting table a staple product of the
hermitcraft server where people don't
clean up after themselves salmon figure
appeared on well there's a couple right
there
a
the salmon ghost is that did i just get
one
that that that that's the thing
i can't believe it yeah this is it it's
totally a salmon head
hold on hold on let me get the let me
get my cat out of the way
okay
all right hello
uh hello sir
um i have a couple of questions for you
if you uh if you would indulge me with
uh i don't answer my door i'm sorry
[Music]
yeah it's the big it's like the big ben
sound
[Music]
oh it's absolutely gorgeous i think
korean actually has a plan so coming to
my temporaries our office that i make we
have our uh gertrude the the
receptionist here
hello oh wow jeez yeah don't mind her
she's she's she's she's welcome to
sahara oh my god i think i think we're
not gonna get anything sold with that
type of customer service
oh my goodness
anyway got some sand
i've got lots of sand
i don't know if i want to buy sand from
you thank you
i'm gonna right okay hope you don't mind
this gal
i mean you can sit you can sit on the
sofa i'm gonna sit behind it
with a mustache
you want some sand
i'm gonna go for
did i go for a bad deed the jungler only
does good oh silly um i've fallen into a
pit
okay no okay all right
hello
boys
please
i'm sorry dog
um no i'm not my bad dude my bad it
wasn't etho the whole time it was
good times with the jungler what and i
could have got it could have gone away
with it for you meddling kids and dog
i'm out
[Laughter]
[Music]
good evening and welcome to hermit news
tonight's top stories ariana griande's
new album i'm agreeing with you tops the
chance for 12 weeks in a row this is
absolutely gross i just i feel gross
even though i know that this is a rock
and not bird poop
it just it just feels disgusting
[Music]
about three hours later no wait maybe
four hours later
there's a lot of cows here okay yeah
here we go
welcome to the real madrid
oh
how did i not die come here come here
come here
no no no no no no no
i'm gonna join you
so you've made
a
so when i was breeding all those cows a
little while ago in here some of them
just basically wondered into this
this tube
and then
[Laughter]
this guy is going to be conquered i
thought that was actually
sorry i thought this was you
i
thought this was you that's life i i
don't know who's still i don't see who's
still going oh
impulse
yes yes yes
where is he
oh
let's go
no no
[Music]
no
i'm out i need to know something can you
dispense great oh
you can
that is amazing depends if i throw
something in here it doesn't doesn't
know what oh is it gonna bring me
potatoes
i'm guessing that this doesn't work and
that i maybe shouldn't have thrown
potatoes in it i don't know what's going
on there but they're stuck on the same
oh no someone sent stuff here
oh
yeah we have no stock at the moment this
is what this shows um right
someone must have something in the
system
i have not i've not buy the second lamp
means that it's failed no it's found a
decoder and then it's failed to shoot
out the shulker box that's weird so it
must have been an item that wasn't in
the system what the so you're telling me
that it's broken
well it's not broken it's just it's just
someone sent an item in that shouldn't
be sent in to the system oh
that's um
not good
he's looking at me directly no he's he's
there oh he knows what he's up to he's
straight up looking at me
no way
he's joined
the fight he's joined the competition
[Laughter]
very nice scar
very very very good what do these do
oh
this is amazing
he hasn't labeled them though
it breaks them all or some of them
that's confusing oh
wow
now this is fun
[Music]
group anymore
you can't speak anything right
geez
oh that's quite a fall
well
i did right i swear i right clicked that
i mean predictable nonetheless
predictable
the house is too tall mate
oh
new farm very unstable
please do not touch
i'm sorry i've got to check this out
oh i don't
i'll go for it i'll go for it
oh no oh
and now we got it
it's chocolatara
yes nailed it
this is the best
leaflet campaign that has ever been made
very sad day so i think i should say a
few words for him he was a good villager
he didn't really do much he kind of just
stayed in the house and slept in my bed
you know what he really he really didn't
do a lot for me am i really i'm not
really that upset he's he he hasn't
actually been very useful this is a
really big insight into what mumbo jumbo
carries around he carries around a stack
and a half of diamonds and some leather
trousers
that's really weird
yeah no this is uh two five five build
height i'm at build height yeah uh one
more add one more block to that scar
no two five five is build height no go
and play some block
try and place the block
you guys are the worst
okay all right down you go
okay oh oh oh redstone perfect fancy red
vlogs
yeah
see
oh you're getting some good loot
oh this is good i like it
but you have to remember there's lava at
some point in the game
dude i'm wiping my hand off it was
getting a little sweaty
i'm shaking over here
remember you can you can bail at any
time remember dude i'm determined to get
a diamond i oh emeralds too oh this is
amazing i didn't get this
it goes down really really deep so oh no
no no no no no no
[Music]
[Laughter]
make a little mumbo again let's get his
mustache on here oh there it is last
time
it's brilliant we need to get his
highest eyes yes
get some eyes
[Laughter]
oh he's looking amazing look at that
really brings out his eyes oh beautiful
let's put the trousers on
kiss of finding oh this is so good dude
this is you know this just makes this
victory so much sweeter you know i i
can't walk
okay
literally
what's going on
look there's ren himself he's in he's in
his van what's he doing is he is he is
he on the toilet i think he might be
oh
sorry oh sorry oh
sorry straight up the ladder okay
particularly well hidden
yeah i've been working on a little bit
of covert operation myself right trying
to make sure that they don't see what
we're doing around here yeah so it's not
quote
a key card out before entering
wow that doesn't look cool style at all
i love it
take key card out
i messed it up
instructions at the top weren't clear
fell down i mean yeah i mean
you do you man everything's riding on
you know what i'm gonna i'm gonna go for
it why not
no
oh
seriously
what happened
you got the job impulse there
no one else applied
oh my goodness he's so close
i'm in a bit of a predicament here i
can't move or do anything
without giving myself away
oh my heart my heart my little heart
no i've been a little by my sister we've
been sustained
so can i point out just for a second
that
area 77 have made a gigantic wall
all the way around
their base
but what i want to know is did they
realize that you can walk through it at
every single point that pressure plate
down below we're going to start the
countdown from nine down to zero
you ready
right down there you see straight down
i had to give myself
oh there he goes
oh he started the countdown
dear hippies
you don't know me
i don't know you well that's kind of
keep it that way this cubs
redstone or
what
oh no
yeah yeah maybe i did this so yeah maybe
i did miss something
you sneaky you sneaky man pressing
exactly what you need
i guess i can press as many as i like
no too many too many too many
mistakes i agree with our membership
yeah no before we get on to this
actually yeah um back onto my chair
can you make sure that my chair is
decommissioned i i can't remember if i
decommissioned it you just have to give
it a press
decommissioned
yeah i need to make sure i deactivated
my chair there's a yeah
whoa oh
oh for goodness oh really
[Laughter]
[Music]
nothing on them and all they got to do
they gotta run in obviously there's the
there's the bottom there that isn't
actually magma blocks and then you've
got to break your way out
no
okay go i take the dare let's go baby
yes come on come on
punch your little hand faster you stupid
little minecraft didn't it no dude i'm
running out of bubbles
okay i'm dying
i'm dying
what's going on
[Music]
[Applause]
like this just does nothing i was super
super skeptical there's just like loads
of dispensers underneath
i've got a piece of coal and i've got
what's the matter
i'm sorry just i don't even have to do
anything
we don't even have to do anything we
could just sit here and watch the dead
have a hard time
this is
this is probably the most entertainment
we're gonna get i'll go in first
yep there we go have you got tnt
i got tmt
ready
[Music]
no
yes try every combination
one two
three
[Laughter]
you're literally
and then you fall down no no no no no no
no no no no
careful it didn't work
is that that's the exit okay the exit's
here so basically he's building away
and he goes up and
oh man
there's nothing you can do
look at all the arrows in him
the adventures of someone playing
minecraft who doesn't know that they're
being watched
every everyone has now seen you just get
absolutely wrecked by a skeleton
get him punch him get him get him get
him punch him he's a guy
oh look there he goes
he didn't even fall
he didn't even fall look you can even
see the totem of undying particles
everywhere beat you speech speech speech
speech speech i want to thank i wanna i
wanna thank my my bros
i'm just so grateful i'm just so glad
let's just let's just yeah let's just
celebrate
wait it did work
it did work
it's alive
i thought
it looks like it's going to blow up
there though
oh it is it is to the weird color
anything
[Laughter]
impulse you got a sec at my base
yep bert
bert